Created By Khaled-Klzdddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddd.
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
Hey.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(TIRES SCREECH)
Yo, boy,
you can't park there.
- We're doing business here.
- So are we.
(SCREAMING)
(MAN SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
Move it!
You, come.
Tell everyone
you know from now on
the prostitution on French
Riviera belongs to me.
(NERVOUSLY)
Who are you?
Karasov.
Go now.
Anna, smile.
Smile!
Good girl.
- You wanna work for me?
- Sure.
Good, sweetie.
(CHUCKLES)
(LAUGHS)
Come on, girls.
Get to work.
(MAN YELLS IN RUSSIAN)
(CRYING)
Try to enjoy it, Anna.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
- WOMAN: Anna?
- Yes.
It's me, It's done, we're
all ready for tonight.
- Everything's set up.
- Good.
- Anna?
- Yes.
Are you sure
you want to do this?
We can still cancel
everything, you know?
I can't stop until
I get all the way out.
Okay, we'll do
as we planned.
I love you.
I love you, too.
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(MAN LAUGHS)
FRANK: Technology moves
so fast, doesn't it?
I mean, as soon as you think they
can't come up with something,
(CAR BEEPS) they come
up with something else.
It'll be able to
drive itself soon.
Makes you wonder if guys
like me will be out of it.
But people always need
guys like me, right?
Hand over the keys, boy!
(ALL LAUGH)
(MAN SPEAKS IN FRENCH)
But the keys
won't do you any good.
See, this car only starts with
the driver's unique fingerprints
when I grip the wheel.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Shut up!
You're smart and sharp.
I'm gonna cut you up.
Gimme the keys and blow.
(IN ENGLISH)
Excuse me.
(LAUGHS)
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Hey!
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
Now, here's how
we're going to do this.
Put your hands on
that wheel, and drive.
That's not
a very good plan.
Get in the car!
(CAR BEEPS)
You're gonna make me late.
(GRUNTING)
And I hate being late.
(GROANING)
I told you that
wasn't a good plan.
(SEAT BELT CLICKS)
(TIRES SCREECH)
(GROANS)
You're late.
I'm 38 seconds late.
There's several degrees of early
and only one degree of late.
And that's too late.
(ENGINE STARTING)
- FRANK: So?
- FRANK SENIOR: So what?
FRANK: So how'd it go?
I thought you
didn't ask questions.
I don't ask questions when I'm
on a job, but this is a favor.
Went okay.
So how much did you get?
791.
791,000?
(CHUCKLES)
That sounds like you
did better than okay.
791 euros, that's my
pension from here on.
791 euros a month.
Well...
Happy retirement, Dad.
Thirty-odd years of making good
money and not a moment to spend it.
Now I've got all the time in the
world and not enough money to spend.
If you ask me,
the system's broken.
Pété de canard.
Good enough for you?
I'll tell you
once I taste it.
FRANK: Maybe you should think about
getting a oar of your own, you know.
FRANK SENIOR:
I have my own car.
Then maybe you should
think about using it.
I enjoy our
quality time together.
You do realize I sit
in traffic for a living.
Is that what you do?
I came here
to be closer to you.
And England
wasn't close enough?
Your mother's buried there.
The island is like
a cemetery to me now.
Easy on the drama,
Dad, please.
Just promise me you won't
stick me in the ground, hmm?
Your mother was a good
Catholic and everything,
but when it comes
my time to go,
just throw me on the fire
and feed me to the fish.
(PHONE VIBRATING)
You gonna get that,
Junior?
I don't use the phone
while I'm driving.
MAN: (SINGING) It's a hard
world to get a break in
All the good things
have been taken
But girl there are ways
to make certain things pay
QIAO: Hi, Gina, it's me.
We're all waiting for you.
Please call me.
She's gonna come.
Don't worry.
Can you believe
these girls?
This is how they show
their appreciation.
By being late
for an appointment.
(SPEAKS IN RUSSIAN)
You don't listen to me.
(IN ENGLISH) It's rude.
What if I was a client?
She wouldn't be late then.
But to meet me,
the man who puts the money
in her pockets
and pays her medical bills,
she's late.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
I'm sure that's her.
It better be.
Hi, baby.
Sorry, sorry.
QIAO: Everyone was worried.
Yeah, traffic in this town's a
nightmare and my cell phone died.
Well, when I see
Karasov tonight,
I will tell him
to get you a driver.
Now, that we are all here,
let's get this party going.
My sentiments exactly.
(GASPS)
Yes!
Okay, okay.
Who is she?
I don't know.
She was independent.
She died over here already.
- You got the necklace?
- Yes, do your thing.
Okay.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(WHIRRING)
- GINA: Qiao, ready?
- Ready.
All for one,
one for all.
Let's go.
FRANK: So, what's your plan?
My plan for what?
For the future, Dad.
You must have a plan.
You always have a plan.
Well, I was gonna keep it as a
surprise, but since you asked,
I've been thinking
about buying that.
That's a nice fishing boat for
a guy with a worker's pension.
I've been saving for it.
Yeah, I think
you miss to travel.
I mean, you've been in some
pretty wild places in your time.
Germany in the '80s,
Colombia in the '90s,
Middle East since then.
Evian is a global brand,
and I'm...
Top sales rep.
Yeah.
Yeah, I know, yeah.
Thirty-odd years working as
a rep for a water company,
and you always seem to find yourself
in the most dangerous places,
the most defining moments.
Fall of the Berlin Wall,
collapse of the Medellin cartel,
- and the Taliban...
- Hmm.
don't forget the Taliban.
I bet they like
Evian in Fallujah.
Well, they don't really care
for sparkling water.
They do prefer the flat.
Okay, Dad.
Junior, I don't think you
have one ounce of wiggle room
to moralize to me about
how I earn my living.
- And what you mean by that?
- Oh, nothing.
I'm sure all your clients
are movie stars,
captains of industry,
dignitaries.
I don't ask,
they don't tell.
That should
tell you something.
(VIBRATING)
Oh, look, um, Miss Unknown
is calling again.
And what would make you think
that "Unknown" is a Miss?
I'm just guessing.
Hello?
ANNA: Is this
the Transporter?
(LAUGHS)
That depends who this is.
Hopefully,
your next employer.
I don't do business
over the phone.
Tomorrow then. 2:00 p.m. at the
bar at the Majestic hotel.
How will I know
who you are?
I'll be alone.
(PHONE BEEPS)
You know, in my day, when you
wanted to make a cup of coffee
you just had to boil the
water and strain the grinds.
Now it seems like
you need a PhD.
Dad, you have a PhD.
That's a juicer.
You need a woman
around the house.
acting like haters
Haters acting like...
Just, just acting like haters
Yo, repeat my conversation
I talk just 'bout my haters
'Cause haters love
my pictures
So now I'm getting' funky
Stackin' money off these hoes
Haters actin' like...
...actin' like haters
Yo, repeat my conversation
I talk just about my haters
Them haters love my pictures
So now I'm getting' funky
Stackin' money off these hoes
Any kind of cash
I'm a professional
When it come to ass
When it's getting hot
I'm a professional
Murder alien slang
Extraterrestrial
Bang bang
Leo?
Huh?
Since when
we work together?
Twelve years.
Fifteen.
Fifteen years.
You still don't trust me.
I trust you.
But when it comes to girls,
I'd like to take my time.
(LAUGHS)
Take your time.
- And Yuri...
- Hmm?
is it true that you live
in your plane now?
Yeah, no customs, no taxes, free
like a bird, man. (CHUCKLES)
(LAUGHS)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
- Hold on, Arkady?
- Not now.
There's been an accident.
Da.
They're calling it
an electrical malfunction.
His wife
identified the bodies.
Then what am I doing here?
He was your accountant,
was he not?
Mine and a lot
of other people's.
Did you ask all of them to come
down here to see his body?
I didn't ask you to come
here to see his body.
I asked you to come here
to see hers.
Who is she?
I was hoping
you might tell me.
She appears to be
one of yours.
I'm afraid I don't know
what you're talking about.
The Coeur Brise is hardly a secret,
Mr.Karasov.
Even men in my own department have
spent time with your "hostesses."
That is what
you call them, no?
I'm a legitimate
businessman, Inspector.
I have a lot of people
who work for me.
And I can't possibly
account for all of them.
Of course not. Though
what I can't quite figure
is why one of them would want
to kill your accountant.
I thought you said this was
an electrical accident.
That is what
the hotel is saying.
They haven't had the benefit
of seeing the .9mm slugs
we pulled
from their heads.
They were shot?
At close range.
I suspect whomever did this started
the fire to cover their tracks.
And you think I had
something to do with it.
BECTAOUI: I want to be
perfectly clear.
No one is accusing you
of anything.
Good.
'Cause if you ever do, you
better come with more men.
You think the West
Africans from '95
are trying to get back
into the skin game?
- They're too smart for that.
- Who is then?
I don't know, but when I
find out who they are,
they'll wish they
were someone else.
You called me.
How did you know
it was me?
You said you'd be alone.
Well, she's alone.
Oh, she has a dog
with her.
Dog people usually
say they're with their dog.
Well, I appreciate you
coming to meet me. lam...
- No names.
- What?
That's the first rule.
Someone asks me who you are,
I have plausible deniability.
Better for me,
better for you.
I heard you were like this.
Heard from whom?
Someone you
worked with previously
whose name would
presumably mean nothing
given your first rule.
You're a quick study.
Are there any other rules
I need to know about?
Once the deal is made,
the deal never changes.
You change the deal,
I drive away.
The deal
is for one passenger.
You pick me up,
drop me off.
WAITER: Your whiskey, sir.
- Any packages?
- Two.
- Weight?
- 104 kilos in total.
Is that a problem? I was told
that you can transport anything.
As long as I don't know what it is.
That's the last rule.
Plausible deniability.
When's the pick up?
Tonight. 5:00 p.m. Banque
de Monaco in Monte Carlo.
That's in three hours.
You need to take a nap?
5:01 then I'm gone, clear?
Yes.
I gather my previous employer
mentioned my...
Of course, your fee.
Half now,
half upon delivery.
I'm good at
following the rules.
Good.
All goes well, perhaps we'll work
together again in the future.
Let's not get ahead
of ourselves.
It's me, he left.
You can proceed.
Oh.
Is there a problem?
No, it's just that
it's a Chéteau Cheval Blanc
from the 2005 vintage.
(CHUCKLES) I know,
it says so on the label.
But it's 900 euros.
- Really?
- Yeah.
900... 900 euros?
Oop!
(SIGHS)
(LAUGHS)
Perhaps I can point you
toward an excellent,
and more affordable
selection of local vineyards?
I'll be fine.
Frank...
Do you need anything?
No, I'm good, thanks.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
(BEEPS)
Hello, Junior.
Dad, I don't think I'm going to
be able to make dinner tonight.
Couple of things
I need to take care of.
I'm sorry to hear that, I got us
a really good bottle of wine.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I'll just have to find someone
else to share it with.
That sounds
like a good plan.
Sounds like a perfect idea.
May I be
of some assistance?
Thank you.
Do you mind holding that?
Of course.
(BUZZING)
(GROANS)
Expensive taste.
(TOLLING)
(CLOCK CONTINUES TOLLING)
Nice hair.
Always wanted
to be a blonde.
Where are the packages?
They're coming.
Ten seconds.
Five.
One.
- Okay, all set.
- What's this?
- What?
- What's going on?
Oh, you're asking
questions now?
No, I told you once I set the
deal, the deal doesn't change.
And it hasn't, here are
my two lovely packages.
Gina, 49 kilos,
Qiao, 55 kilos, 104 in all.
We should go.
No, I'm canceling the deal.
You should go.
Out of the car.
All of you, now.
No one is getting out of the
car, asshole, now drive.
You think
this is the first time
someone's held
a gun to my head?
No, I don't.
But it's gonna be the first
time someone uses it.
Oh, she's a charmer.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
Anna, there's a cop.
Okay, we don't have time
to talk about this anymore.
Just show it
to him already.
Show me what?
No good deed
goes unpunished.
Don't mess this up.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Monaco Police.
Vehicle documents, please.
Window!
What is it gonna be, Frank?
Lower the window.
Get out of the vehicle!
Seatbelts, now.
(TIRES SCREECH)
(SIRENS WAILING)
Get my father back on the phone.
I want to talk to him now.
You'll be able to talk
to him all you want
as soon as the job is done.
(HORN HONKING)
Whoo!
ANNA: This is a good time
to lose them, Frank.
FRANK: I'm doing my best.
(GRUNTS)
So what's with all
the getups?
Questions again?
- What about your rules?
- I don't ask names.
But when someone kidnaps my
father, I ask questions.
(SIRENS CONTINUE WAILING)
I guess you're as good
as advertised, Frank.
Thanks.
(IN FRENCH)
All units... Code 3
black Audi S8 in the tunnel.
Copy!
(ENGINE REVS)
Look, you'll be
delivered as promised,
but if anything
happens to my dad...
Stay focused, honey.
Your father will be fine.
What's that?
More company.
(ENGINE REVS)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(SIRENS CONTINUE WAILING)
Watch out.
(GRUNTS)
You weren't kidding.
Kidding's not really
my thing.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
- Okay, let's go.
- What are we doing?
We need to change cars.
Come on.
Let's go.
(CAR BEEPS)
Are we going to leave the car
with all the evidence?
Not really.
(BEEPS)
BANK MANAGER: It's really quite
strange, to tell you the truth.
The Mediterranean Bank
has been robbed before,
but never like this.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Let me show you.
You'll see
a woman right there.
She said
she was Elena Turgin,
wife of one
Stanislav Turgin.
Had a passport and his
safety deposit box's keys
to prove as much.
That's not Elena Turgin.
BANK MANAGER: Yes.
And while I didn't
know that at the time,
I refused to allow
her access nonetheless.
As only Mr. Turgin
is authorized.
But as you will see,
I was coerced.
First girl took my keys.
With both sets, she could open
the security box by herself.
There was nothing
I could do to stop her.
And who was on
the security post?
Hmm.
Voilé.
They all look exactly the same.
You cannot tell them apart.
There's one more thing.
Getaway driver.
He picked the one girl up,
and then waited for the two
others to arrive moments later.
The police found the car,
what was left of it.
It was set fire to,
but they were already gone.
Of course they were.
(PHONE RINGING)
Oh, Excuse me.
Yes? I'll be right there.
An inspector from Nice.
If you'll wait for me just a
minute, I'll be right back.
What do you think?
They're either our girls,
or someone who's trying to pass
themselves off as our girls.
I will do an inventory and
check with the competition.
See if there's anyone
unaccounted for.
First Turgin at the hotel,
and now this?
Don't worry, we will find
who and make him pay.
(BEEPS)
Late again, Junior.
Junior?
You're okay, Dad?
Well, I've been sucker
punched a lot in my time,
but never by a girl.
Stop right there.
How many more
of you are there?
She's the last one.
She is Estonian.
From Tallinn.
I've done some funky shit in my
time down there, I can tell you.
Actually they've got very,
very good vodka.
That's great, Dad.
If I were armed,
you'd know it by now.
Your father sure is.
(CHUCKLES)
He's clean.
Here's the rest
of what we owe you.
Thank you very much.
Now if you'll untie him so we can
leave and never see you again.
I'm afraid
I can't do that.
We're not done
with you just yet.
I'm disappointed, I thought
you were all natural blondes.
What do you want?
I wanna make a new deal.
Thanks, but I think
I'll pass.
You haven't heard
the terms yet.
This should be good.
They're really
very simple.
We're going to pay
someone a visit,
and you're going to make sure
that we get there and back
without
any more incidents.
I'm not sure I see how much of
a deal that really is for me.
The deal for you is that
your father gets to live.
So you're gonna shoot him?
Then what? You still
have me to contend with.
You think
we're stupid, Frank?
That hurts my feelings.
ANNA: I wouldn't do that if I were you.
That touches your skin,
it's nearly as toxic as the dose
your father drank in his beer.
Headaches,
vomiting, convulsions,
all leading up
to an eventual death.
Soup to nuts, it will kill
a man in 12 hours.
I should kill you right now.
All of you.
You could do that,
but you'd be killing
your father along with us.
It will take the lab more than
12 hours to find out what it is.
And you have the antidote?
You play ball,
your father gets it.
You don't, he dies.
How do I know you're gonna hold
up your end of the bargain?
Did I ever lie to you?
Besides, you don't have
much of a choice.
I got all the girls that most fit
the description on the video.
They're all here?
All but four.
So one of them is the
dead girl from the hotel.
And the others
are our thieves.
What did they get
from the safe deposit box?
KARASOV: Some cash,
jewelry, documents.
Far as I know, Turgin didn't
leave very much in there.
Still doesn't explain
the driver.
You know him,
don't you?
We go way back.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Da. MAN: Excuse me for
disturbing you, sir.
But there are police officers
approaching the yacht.
Tell them
I'm in a meeting.
Get lmasov and Yuri
on the phone.
All in all, it's not
the worst way to go.
I always thought I'd end up being shot.
Left to rot somewhere.
Excuse me,
but now we're partners,
maybe you can tell me
what this is all about?
You do what we ask,
I think you'll find that the more you
venture, the more you will gain.
Quoting Alexandre Dumas?
Like, what?
You're Count D'Artagnan
and they're
the Three Musketeers?
You've read it.
In fact, my favorite line is,
"I'm sure you're very nice,
"but you'd be nicer
if you left me alone.
No deal, Junior.
Zip me up.
Mmm, Don't look so sad.
In 24 hours,
this will all be over.
And once you understand
what we're up to,
you might even like it.
Stop right here.
What are we doing here?
Do you wanna play doctor?
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
How long have you been
working for the Coeur Brisé?
I saw your necklace.
Since I was 12.
I suppose now you understand how
I know your former employer.
Karasov, we didn't exactly leave
things on the best of terms.
I'm surprised
he'd recommend me.
He didn't.
But I overheard him
on plenty of occasions
telling other people
that you're the best.
Called the best by one of
the worst on the planet.
I'm not sure
how to feel about that.
Hello, who's the
anesthesiologist on call?
WOMAN: That would be
Dr. Benet.
Right, of course. Can you connect
me with central supply, please?
- MAN: Central supply.
- FRANK: Yeah, I'm Dr. Smith, calling for Dr. Benet.
We're gonna be operating
on a US citizen
and we're running low
on Neroflurax in OR-6.
I'll send someone up.
Yeah, don't bother,
I'm already on my way.
(DOOR BUZZES)
Dr. Smith?
That's me.
Neroflurax.
You sign here.
- I'll grab it.
- Perfect.
But I also need
your stamp right here.
Okay, sure.
Done!
Let's go.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Everything okay?
Another shot of vodka?
Sure.
(IN ENGLISH) Your accent,
what is it? Meridional?
You can tell
it's meridional?
Well, you don't get to hear
the Languedoc much these days
except from
rural old farts.
They love their Occitan.
My parents are from
the Basque Country
- in the Pyrenees.
- The Pyrenees.
I know
the Basque country well.
How do you know it?
Was a big aerospace industry
tucked in all around there.
Warheads,
helicopter turbo shafts...
I ran many sorts of parts to all
sorts of places in the Middle East.
Basque people
are good people.
I love that
poulet basquaise.
You cook?
(IN FRENCH)
Sure.
(IN ENGLISH)
And you?
But of course.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
- They got the gas.
- We're up.
They got the gas.
They got the gas,
okay.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
Any of you
speak english?
ALL: No, no, no.
Any of you want
to make a thousand euros?
ALL: Yeah, sure!
Let's go.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
Hi.
How about a drink?
How about your room?
YURI: How the hell did
they rob a bank?
They'd have
to have his...
He did, they did.
Someone did.
I'm calling everyone.
Until I figure out
what's going on,
be on the look out
for anything strange. okay?
Okay.
Call the pilot,
Let's get out of here.
We can't take off.
It's too late.
I want to be on the wheels up
the minute regulations allow.
Yes, sir.
(DOOR OPENS)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Please,
make yourself comfortable.
No, you make
yourself comfortable.
Get undressed.
Seatbelts, please.
(SIGHS)
(SEATBELTS CLICK)
FRANK: Three girls dressed the same to
rob a bank so no one knows who's who.
Are you asking me
or telling me?
See, the thing
I can't figure out is
why one of you stays behind and
misses out on all the fun.
In The Three Musketeers,
there were really four.
One of us had to stay behind
and look after dear old dad.
No, No, I don't think
that's it.
You could have left him
tied up in the boot.
Maybe we're smarter
than the Three Musketeers.
You're not that smart
if you're calling him "old."
(SCOFFS)
Hey, jerk-off! You can't park here!
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTING)
I'll swap the tanks and
we meet back here, okay?
ANNA: Come on.
Let's do this.
(TECHNO MUSIC PLAYING)
Hey, you! what you
think you're doing?
I got you fresh smoke.
But the guy 'gust
changed the tanks.
It's expired, there's a warning
right on the label, Look.
(GRUNTS)
(MAN WHISTLES)
He wasn't feeling well.
Can you give me the key?
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
Hey!
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
Go!
(ALL SHOUTING)
(BANGING ON DOOR)
(TICKING)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
(ALL CHEERING)
(ALL COUGHING)
(ALL GRUNTING)
(COUGHING)
(MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING)
(GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
I get
the fingerprints.
I'll keep an eye out.
- ANNA: Okay, help me.
- Okay.
ANNA: Right there.
(BEEPING)
(GROANS)
- They're all out.
- All right.
(BEEPS)
ANNA: Good.
(GROANS)
(GRUNTING)
Okay, baby,
it's coming.
All right, I'm in.
I hope
the transfer code works.
ANNA: We're gonna find out.
All right, let's try.
(MEN GRUNTING)
ANNA: Here we go.
Okay, hold on.
(BEEPS)
Yes! All good.
Come on, let's go!
Let's get
the hell out of here.
(GRUNTS)
Shit.
Where the hell is he?
(CELL PHONE VIBRATES)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(GAGGING)
Yes?
It's not nice to keep ladies
waiting alone in a dark alley.
Whoever those ladies are,
tell them I'm on my way.
All right.
Hey, you should have
just given me the key.
(DOOR CLOSES)
- GINA: Where is he?
- I don't know!
GINA: ls he drinking tea
or what?
What took you so long?
There was a couple of babies
I had to put to sleep.
Shit! Seems some of
the babies just woke up.
And they look cranky.
Come on, let's go.
(CAR BEEPS)
Wait for me here.
And don't touch anything.
(BEEPS)
(GROANS)
What?
Where is he going?
- Shit!
- GINA: Anna, stop the car!
ANNA: He said
don't touch anything.
Okay, he's got this.
He's got this!
(GROANS)
Gina! I don't know if I
trust this guy, Anna!
(MEN GRUNTING)
ANNA: Oh, shit.
No, I think we should
hit the brakes now.
No, he said don't
touch anything, No!
Anna!
(GROANS)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
GINA: Stop the car!
Anna, do it now!
- I can't do it!
- I can try.
Hit the brakes!
The gate!
Hurry up!
(TIRES SCREECH)
Hold on tight.
Oh, God.
BOTH: No! No!
ANNA: Seriously?
FRANK: We're late, My dad
hates it when I'm late.
What are we waiting for?
It's almost 6:00 a.m.
Well, the captain's
on his way, Mr. Yuri.
We'll be off as soon
as regulations permit.
Oh, God.
Good morning, sir!
Good morning, Mr. Yuri.
Who are you?
I'm your pilot,
Captain Martinet.
Captain Guesdon's
replacement.
What the hell is this?
Well, this is embarrassing.
I'd assumed that he told you.
Um, he's sick, food poisoning.
Oysters, I believe he said.
(SPEAKS IN RUSSIAN)
Call him up.
(SIGHS)
(VIBRATES)
Hello, Mr. Yuri.
YURI: I'm told
you are sick, Guesdon.
Yes, oysters.
The pilot who has come in your
stead, you vouch for him?
Yes, I highly
recommend him.
He is a decorated pilot.
Okay, well, feel better.
Thank you.
I want to be in the air
as soon as possible.
We shall do our
very best, sir.
This is the captain speaking,
we are cleared for take-off.
Good morning,
Air Star 669.
Please wait for
take-off clearance.
Would you like something
to drink, Mr. Yuri?
Champagne?
Orange juice?
Ah, well,
champagne is good.
Champagne,
coming right up.
Leave us, go away.
Your champagne,
Mr. Yuri.
Thank you.
Would you like
anything else?
Yeah, tell the pilot
to get a move on
and then come
and keep me company.
Sure.
Electrical board checked,
yaw dampers
on and operating.
Rudder trimmer checked.
Ready when you are,
Captain.
Proceed to main runway.
FRANK SENIOR: Good morning, this
is the captain speaking again.
We are third in line
for take-off.
Please fasten
your seat belts.
We should be
in the air momentarily.
Finally.
What the hell?
(VIBRATING)
Hello?
Hmm.
3-1, O-5.
(BEEPING)
Yes!
MAN: (ON RADIO)
Air Star 669.
Please make your way
to the main runway.
And wait to be
cleared for take-off.
Thank you,
Air Traffic Control.
(BEEPS)
Oh, hang on.
We have an alert.
It's probably
just a blown fuse.
Probably just a blown fuse?
It's no wonder you're still
in that bloody chair!
Air Star 669 to tower.
We're gonna have to run...
We're good.
Let's get off this plane.
Air Star 669 to tower...
MAN: (ON RADIO) Tower to
Air Star 669, do you copy?
I repeat, do you copy?
This way!
Tower to Air Star 669,
hold your position!
Mr. Yuri! Everything okay in there?
Mr. Yuri?
Sir!
(ALARM BEEPING)
I was talking
to your friend Gina.
There's a huge aerospace industry
in the Pays Basque region.
What?
In the Pyrenees.
Don't worry.
Never mind!
Call security immediately.
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
Don't say it.
How can you be late?
What kind of
Special Forces were you?
Where are you, Dad?
Listen, there's been a complication, son.
We're trapped.
We're in the main
compartment cargo area.
Do you have any idea
how to get us out of here?
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(ALARM RINGING)
(SIRENS WAILING)
Are you towards
the front wheel?
No, no,
it's the main cargo hatch.
Stop the plane!
I repeat, stop the plane!
Climb in the back.
I'm gonna need you
to count for me.
Okay, I'm going to count to
five and you're going to jump.
What do you mean, jump?
What? No! We can't jump!
FRANK SENIOR: Junior!
Five!
- FRANK: Four!
- ANNA: Four!
Three!
Two!
ANNA: Two!
One!
ANNA: One!
(BRAKES SCREECH)
How bad is it?
It's really bad!
Take the scarf and
put pressure on it!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
GINA: It's not working,
we need a doctor.
If we don't outrun
these guys,
we're gonna need
a bloody good lawyer too.
Tower to Air Star 669,
you are going to crash.
Do you copy?
669, do you copy?
I repeat,
you are going to crash.
You need to stop
the engine right now!
- Wake up!
- MAN: (ON RADIO):If you hear me,
you need to pull
the emergency brake!
It's the trigger
on your right.
Yeah, yeah, I see it.
Do it now!
(ENGINE STOPS)
(GASPS)
She's convulsing!
QIAO: What do we do?
You hold on!
- You see the building, Junior?
- I do.
Well, planes tend to move,
buildings tend to stand still.
- That's what I'm counting on.
- No, no ,no ,no!
I see what you're thinking.
- And?
- I hate it!
(ALL SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
- Holy...
- What the hell?
The unidentified vehicle has
just entered the main terminal.
(WOMAN ANNOUNCING
IN FRENCH)
(HORN HONKING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
Come on!
(HORN HONKING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
Frank!
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
QIAO: Okay, hold on.
Yeah, okay.
You gotta help her.
Don't look at me.
I did my part.
I got you there and back.
Now, give me the antidote.
Frank!
She can bleed out
for all I care.
Junior!
Once the deal is set,
the deal doesn't change.
The deal was my time
for the antidote.
There is no antidote!
Excuse me?
It's just water
in the vial.
There's nothing in his beer.
We made it up.
So he's not gonna die?
Not from poison.
(SIGHS) Be a dear and get me
some rags and water, would you?
Look, the bullet
is still in there.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
If we don't get it out and
the bleeding doesn't stop
she is gonna die.
All right, we've wasted enough
time getting here already.
We all agreed, no doctors.
No. No, we can't just
let her die.
QIAO: We knew
it would be dangerous.
Okay, no doctors.
Let's help her ourselves.
Can you pass me
that bottle, would you?
Dad, you.
Dad, you can't...
Don't worry, son.
It's focus for me.
Okay, here's the water.
Oh, thanks, love.
"Love?
You know, she's from
Pays Basque, Pyrenees.
Dad, that's great, Dad.
Can you get something
to raise her leg up, please.
See if you can find
some perfume,
some tweezers and if
there's any sugar around.
QIAO: Okay.
What do you want
me to do with it?
All right, take the rod off
one of those clothes racks
and wrap this
around the end.
What to do?
To do what?
FRANK SENIOR: And swab
all the corners of the room.
See how many cobwebs
you can get on there.
- Cobwebs?
- S'il vous plait.
Here.
FRANK: You handle a lot of triage
in your time as a sales rep?
FRANK SENIOR: What can I tell you?
Those boys at Evian,
they play rough.
FRANK: You could use
the vodka.
Don't be ridiculous, son.
That's a waste of good vodka.
Right, now listen, she may look
like she's out cold, right?
But she's gonna feel this.
I need you to hold her down.
Okay, All right.
Sorry about this, Maria,
but it is the only way.
(GRUNTS)
(GASPING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
- You got it?
- It's...
FRANK SENIOR:
Hurry with the cobwebs!
- All right, thanks.
- Yeah.
(GROANS)
What does that do?
The sugar disinfects the wound
and cobwebs coagulate the blood.
It's not exactly
the Cleveland Clinic,
but it's going
to keep her alive
until we get her
patched up properly.
Put some pressure on that,
would you, Junior?
You're okay.
Shh, you're okay.
No one's dying today.
IMASOV: Look who's there.
Same girls,
different outfits.
How did this happen?
One second
everything is fine,
the next I wake up
on the floor.
It's some kind of
medical grade anesthetic.
They switched the tank
for the fog machine.
One part I can't quite
figure out though is
why your girls
would rob me.
Don't be ridiculous.
Just the same as I heard they
robbed Turgin's safe deposit box.
You can't think I had
anything to do with this.
I'm not sure
what to think.
But it appears that someone
else is working with them.
You and he know each other,
if I recall.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
It's Yuri.
Da.
(YURI SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(IN OTHER LANGUAGE)
Of course not.
I'll get to the bottom
of it.
Yuri got hit as well.
Another Coeur Brisé.
Awfully convenient,
don't you think?
Two of us get robbed
by your girls
and a friend from
your illustrious past.
Give me six hours. I'll find
them and I'll take care of it.
Let's go.
(POP MUSIC PLAYING)
Are they broken?
They've been worse.
Let me see.
I'll be okay.
(FRANK SENIOR
AND GIRLS LAUGHING)
What about your dad?
Looks like
they made it up to him.
I can't remember the
last time either of them
slept in the same bed
as the men who pay them.
I don't think he paid.
Well...
Something else?
Yes.
I wanted to thank you for
what you've done for us.
I'm sorry I lied to you
about the poison.
How about being sorry you kidnapped
my father in the first place?
I'm sorry about that, too.
It was wrong for me
to use your father,
and it was wrong
for me to use you.
Very wrong.
I think our deal is done.
Yeah.
Don't you want to know
what I'm going to do next?
I think I have a good idea.
I'm talking about
the future.
Tell me about the future.
I'm going to finish
what we started.
How did you get
caught up in all of this?
I come from
an impoverished village.
Drinking and drugs killed
the people that guns didn't.
And then when I was 12,
I came home from the factory
where I worked
and my mother introduced me
to a man in a very nice suit.
Karasov.
He said I could come and do
work for him in warm places.
He would give me
food and clothes
and introduce me
with men for money.
I looked at my mom
and she said it was okay.
"Yeah, go.
And so I did.
It wasn't until later that I found
out that she sold me to him.
For $500.
Jesus, Anna.
I think she could
have gotten $600, right?
(CHUCKLES)
You don't need
to do this, you know.
You can still walk away.
If we stop now, it will have
been for nothing,
everything I went through.
Do you know
what it feels like
to be thought of as trash?
He'll kill you, you know.
Without thinking about it.
It's like the Count
said to his Musketeers,
"I don't cling to life
sufficiently to fear death.
(EXHALES)
Dad, time to go.
Really?
- Excuse me, ladies.
- Mmm, Mmm.
(SHUSHING)
WOMAN: (SINGING)
Cause I'm a fool for you
You know I speak the truth
Whatever you say or do
You know they're doing
another job.
Yeah, taking on a Russian crime
lord is more of a suicide mission.
Imagine how horrible your life has
to be to try something like that.
I've seen some horrible things
in some horrible places.
Being sold into prostitution
with death as your only out.
That's about
as bad as it gets.
The question is, what are
you gonna do about it?
Me?
There's no one
else in the car.
I don't have
to do anything.
I'm gonna drop you home,
ditch the car at a chopper,
go to Paris for a bit until
things cool down, you know.
That doesn't sound
like the man I raised.
Dad, stop.
All right,
stay within the lines,
watch everything play out, that's
exactly what a fobbit would do.
Look, my entire life, I've tried
to do the right thing, you know.
Maybe I wasn't a spy
like you,
but I served that fool.
What did it get me?
Shit I didn't deserve.
You said it yourself.
It doesn't mean you stop
doing the right thing.
Send me a postcard
from Paris.
(SIGHS)
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
- Dad?
- KARASOV: Hello, Frank.
Don't tell me you don't recognize my voice.
It hasn't been that long.
What do you want?
Well, I want to make a deal.
You have some people I want,
three of them to be exact,
and I have someone you want.
Go ahead, say hello.
FRANK SENIOR: Drive away.
Wherever you are,
just drive away...
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Dad... Put him back
on the phone.
KARASOV: Well,
he's resting now
and frankly, I think
he's giving you bad advice.
Anything happens to him...
You'll what? Kill me?
Come on, Frank, I know you.
You were a good soldier.
And you'll do what
a good soldier always does.
You'll follow the orders, So
listen to me very closely.
If you ever wish to see
your father alive again,
you'll do exactly
what I say.
(PHONE BEEPS)
Son of a bitch!
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
- A big, black SUV.
- Occupants?
(CAR APPROACHING)
Couldn't stay away?
There's a new deal.
I thought you
said you never...
That was before
he took my dad.
Listen, I'm in this shit because
of you and so is my dad.
So whether you agree or not
we're going to see Karasov
on his yacht right
now with the ledger.
I was all for you, now I
need you to do one for me.
Do we have
a choice?
Not really.
We'll help you.
No more games.
No more bullshit.
Where's Gina?
She left.
Back to her family.
Don't lie to me.
Karasov assumes that there
is only three of us
and that's what he is looking for.
Don't you think?
This is why we always
kept someone separate.
So one of us could get away.
That was our deal.
Let's get
your father back.
Welcome back, girls.
Been a long time.
Not long enough.
Still upset
about what happened?
A little bit, yeah.
I thought you John Wayne types
just let it roll off your back.
That was the old days.
Now we hold grudges
and get revenge.
Revenge for what?
That car of yours
is a real step up
from driving
a military convoy truck.
You know, you brought this
on yourself, Frank.
Everyone in your platoon played
ball, they made a lot of money.
It would have been easier
if you just went along
with the rest, you know.
I wasn't there to make money.
I was there to fight a war.
I don't play ball
with people like you.
Well, I can't speak
to the arrangements
your country's military
makes to get jobs done.
I'm just happy I was on the
side that profited from it.
Well, let's just hope you
get what's coming to you.
Qiao, Anna, Maria,
glad you could join us.
Where's my dad?
Did one of you
bring the ledger?
Now where's my dad?
I said...
I heard you.
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
I assume you have
a plan, Junior.
What is this?
You tell us.
What's that supposed
to mean?
You called
the meeting.
I didn't call anything.
Cut this shit.
What's this about?
Well, for one, I found the
people who stole from you.
Right, And he's
right there.
Listen, I'm getting pretty
sick of you both accusing me
of something
I didn't do.
As a matter of fact, I brought
these people here to kill them.
He's lying.
Who the hell
are you?
I'm Anna and
I work for him.
He told me to
rob you and I did.
We called you here because
he has your money.
Let her talk.
ANNA: There's no way we're
taking the fall for this.
'Cause he robbed you.
Not us.
You lying bitch.
Have him show you, Ask him to
show you the bank account.
I'm not showing
anybody shit.
We've been friends
for a long time.
Maybe you should.
You'll see
he has every penny.
Shut up!
It's not part of your plan,
this, is it, Junior?
I checked the account this morning.
I have just over 120 million.
I'm gonna lower my gun.
Grab that tablet right there.
Show you the account, You're
gonna see for yourself.
That's a fair start.
Come on, baby.
Come on.
Yeah!
Okay.
Yes!
Thanks for the code,
asshole!
Okay!
$120 million.
Just as I said.
Give it to me.
This doesn't make sense.
Don't have the money, huh?
What the hell
did you do?
Exactly what you told me.
I'm gonna rip you up.
No!
ANNA: Maria!
Shit!
Come on.
Say goodbye
to your money.
You think you can untie the
boat and get it started?
I'll try!
What?
What's the plan, Junior?
I'll hold them Off.
We meet back
on the boat in two minutes!
- Can you give me four?
- Okay.
Cover fire!
Oh, you got to be kidding.
Why do you never carry a gun?
You ever think about
being less critical?
Come on, come on,
let's go!
Okay, On my count!
Three, two, one! Go! go! go!
Okay.
MAISSA: Shit.
(GRUNTS)
(CHOKING)
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
You jerk!
Dammit!
(GROANS)
Gina! No, no,
no, no, no.
Stay with me!
(WEAKLY) It's okay.
It's okay.
Stay with me, stay with me.
I'm sorry, Frank.
No, no, no.
- I'm sorry.
- Stay with me.
Faster! Go here!
- Get on the jet ski!
- BODYGUARD: Yes, sir.
Hold on!
Come on!
(SCREAMS)
Don't move!
Frank!
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(SCREAMING)
Come on!
You should have joined me when
you had the chance, Frank.
(GROANS)
(YELLS)
(SOBBING)
Don't move!
You set this up.
You called the
meeting on the yacht
and made sure
my dad was kidnapped,
so I'd be here to help
you finish the job.
Stay where you are!
And now you're going to shoot
me because I'm a loose end.
The last person left
to name you for your crimes.
I can't stop until I
get all the way out.
The question is, if you were
supposed to kill me then,
why did you save my life?
(SOBBING)
Stop.
Please stop.
Your friends
died for you, Anna.
Like I would have
died for them.
I just hope whatever you
got out of it was worth it.
(SNIFFLES)
I'm so sorry.
You'd better go.
That's the deal?
That's the deal.
FRANK SENIOR: I'll tell you again,
but it won't be any different.
I work for Evian.
I was delivering water.
I get there, there are
dead bodies everywhere.
Then two guys roar off
on a speedboat and a jet ski.
This one?
On the boat, yeah.
- And the jet ski?
- I don't know!
Because whoever he was,
he will be tried for murder.
Look, I can't tell you what I don't know.
I didn't see the guy.
(SCOFFS)
How convenient.
I guess we're
done here, right?
'Cause if not, then please
charge me with something,
otherwise you're
wasting both our times.
You can go.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Thank you, Inspector.
Very good of you.
Goodbye.
Crime Czar Murdered?
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
Twelve hours
in a police station.
Do you know how humiliating
that is for me?
Why don't you tell me all about
it over a good bottle of wine?
Finally you say
something smart.
MAN: (SINGING) Maybe we should, maybe
we should knock on heaven's door
We don't need to go
to the liquor store
You give me that high
Get me high
It's better than gold
You're making it hard
For me to go slow
You give me that high
It's better than gold
You're making it hard
Please, don't you act
so ruthlessly
Oh, we're fanatical
Rabid animals
Please, no one needs
your point of view
No, we're fanatical
Rabid animals
Please, don't you act
so ruthlessly
Oh, we are cannibals
Rabid animals
(PHONE CHIMES)
Please, no one needs
your point of view
Oh, rabid animals
Rabid animals
Oh, good Lord,
life is bitter and sweet
Sometimes on my knees
Sometimes on my feet
(CHIMING)
You give me that high
Get me high
It's better than gold
You're making it hard
Mama!
For me to go slow
You give me that high
It's better than gold
You're making it hard
Please, don't you act
so ruthlessly
We're fanatical
Rabid animals
Please, no one needs
your point of view
No, we're fanaticals
Rabid animals
Please, don't you act
so ruthlessly
Oh, we are cannibals
Rabid animals
Please, no one needs
your point of view
Oh, rabid animals
Rabid animals
MAN: (ON RECORDING) If you ever
meet them, don't hesitate-
(MUSIC ENDS)
(MUSIC STARTS)
WOMAN: (SINGING) Red
lipstick on your pillowcase
Look at you You've been
down for the chase
Quick as a whip
And sharp as a knife
Make you a promise
The ride of your life
Doesn't have to make sense
And I'd rather
fight back again
All alone
Baby, don't you see
If I can't have you
You can't have me
On my own
within my fantasies
If I can't have you
You can't have me
Velvet curtains
and a fireplace
Leather couches
and rose bouquets
Torn by my senses
I'm paralyzed
I've gone too far to realize
Doesn't have to make sense
And I'd rather
fight back again
All alone
Baby, don't you see
If I can't have you
You can't have me
On my own
Within my fantasies
If I can't have you
You can't have me
Oh, you can't have me
Oh, oh
Oh, you can't,
you can't, you can't
No, you can't,
No, no
You can't, you can't,
you can't
(VOCALIZING)
All alone
Baby, don't you see
If I can't have you
You can't have me
On my own
And in my fantasies
If I can't have you
You can't have me
No, no
(VOCALIZING)
All alone
Baby, don't you see
If I can't have you
You can't have me
On my own
And in my fantasies
If I can't have you
You can't have me
No, no
(VOCALIZING)
You can't have me